<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plants>
    <plant><id>1</id><name>AMERICAN AGAVE MEDIOPICTA ALBA GRAY-GREEN H80 D 35CM</name><price>492.41$</price><description>Agave Americana Mediopicta Alba (Agave Americana Mediopicta Alba) - this agave is the winner of the prestigious award of garden merit of the Royal Horticultural Society. It grows up to 120 cm in height and up to 180 cm in diameter.It is an evergreen perennial that forms magnificent rosettes of thick prickly silver-green and slightly curved leaves, which are decorated with a bright creamy-white stripe in the center. The fleshy leaves are armed with curved spikes and a long tip of red or brown color. When blooming, it forms a long stem (up to 4-4,5 m in height) on which beautiful, large, greenish - yellow flowers are located.</description></plant>
    <plant><id>2</id><name>AGAVE GEMINIFLORA GREEN H55 D30 CM</name><price>185.48$</price><description>It can have 100-200 leaves, which are linear, stiff, dark green and have convex edges with white horny lines and curled threads. The flowers are 5 or 6 centimeters long on a high inflorescence.</description></plant>
    <plant><id>3</id><name>QUEEN VICTORIA GREEN AGAVE H30 D23 CM</name><price>256.47$</price><description>Queen Victoria's compact agave is the most aesthetically attractive species. The leaves are stiff, elongated triangular in shape, with a brown tip, keeled on the underside, have a white border. At the end of each leaf there is one rather long thorn 1-2 cm and usually a couple of shorter ones. Some plants can reach 60 cm in diameter. And usually the rosette of leaves is about 40 cm in diameter. The compact form grows no more than 30 cm in height.</description></plant>
    <plant><id>4</id><name>FILAMENTOUS AGAVE (FILIFERA) GREEN H55 D35 CM</name><price>256.47$</price><description>The perennial is native to Southern California. It forms a rosette of fleshy gray-green leaves 20-70 cm long and 4.5–10 cm wide.Life expectancy is more than 100 years.  Blooms in adulthood after 20 years.  There are numerous yellow funnel - shaped flowers 3-6 cm long on the panicle . Even without flowers, this herbaceous plant has a high decorative value. Strict forms of agave are perfect for decorating the central place on a flower bed, mini-ponds, mixborders or low fences. It will look great both in a single landing on the lawn and in a group. In the northern regions, it can be grown as a container plant. Agaves are plants for "lazy" gardeners or those who have catastrophically not enough time, even to water the plants. They are unpretentious in care, for a long time (up to 6 months or more) they can feel great without watering, even if they were not watered in a timely manner. An excellent variety with good symmetry and shape.</description></plant>
    <plant><id>5</id><name>AGLAOMORPH JIM H50 D17 CM</name><price>44.11$</price><description>Aglaomorph fern is not popular among flower growers. It is native to the tropical moist forests of Central and South America. To plant such a plant, a large spacious container will be required, since its shaggy rhizome is very large and creeping. Such a fern, like many others, has fairly wide leaves (vaya), which can reach 50 centimeters in length. And on them there are narrow and wide leaves. Aphids and mealyworms mainly settle on the aglaomorph.</description></plant>
</plants>